Bush, E. Ogden; Papers apap233
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
E. Ogden Bush Papers
1884, 1958-1965
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Bush, E. Ogden
apap233
9.6 cubic ft.
The E. Ogden Bush Papers document Bush's service as a New York State Senator in the early 1960s.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted with the exception of several folders marked below.
Acquisition Information
E. Ogden Bush initially donated his papers to Syracuse University in 1965. In 2006, the papers were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical Sketch
Elmer Ogden Bush was born on September 14, 1898 in DeLancey, New York. His early schooling took place in a one-room schoolhouse. He graduated from the Delaware Academy at Delhi. In January 1920, he graduated from the University of Buffalo with the degree of Doctor of Dentistry.
He married Ella Vitt on May 9, 1925, and they had four children.
Before he embarked upon his political career, Senator Bush was a successful dentist. From 1933 to 1937, he served in the New York State Assembly representing Delaware County. In 1957, he was elected to the New York State Senate as a Republican and served until 1965 in the 34th District. For twelve years, he also served as the Delaware County Republican Chairman, but in 1959 he lost that position to Edwyn E. Mason. Bush was a member of the American Legion, Farm Bureau, and the Freemasons. He was the president of the Delaware County Broadcasting Company and of the Council at Delhi Agricultural and Technical Institute (now SUNY Delhi). Bush Hall on the campus of SUNY Delhi is named for him. He was also the director of the First National Bank and Trust Company of Walton, and he was an operator of Station WDLA at Walton.
Scope and Contents
The E. Ogden Bush Papers document his work as a New York Senator during the years 1958-1965. The papers include legislative bills and files, newspapers, correspondence, resolutions, and various published materials. The subject files include the major topics of conservation, education, highways, motor vehicles, labor, Delaware County, Greene County, Sullivan County, Ulster County, and teachers. The bulk of the collection dates from Bush's later tenure as a State Senator from 1960 to 1965, rather than from his first term in office. Please note that the collection does not include materials related to his service in the New York State Assembly.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Subject Files, 1884, 1958-1965, Undated
Series 2 - Legislative Bills, 1959-1965, Undated
Series 1 is arranged alphabetically and Series 2 is arranged chronologically by bill number.
Politics and Politicians; Natural resources--New York (State); Pigeons--New York (State); Teachers--New York (State); New York (State)--Politics and government; Correspondence; Legislative Records; Articles; Clippings (information artifacts); Memorandums; Bush, E. Ogden; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979; State University of New York Agricultural and Technical Institute (Delhi, N.Y.); Republican Party (N.Y.); New York (State). Legislature. Senate; New York (State). Legislature. Senate. Committee on Finance.
- Subject Files, 1884; 1958-1965; Undated; 1; 7.8 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1 contains subject files covering a wide assortment of topics including conservation, education, various New York counties, and labor. Correspondence and news clippings are kept within the subject files. Miscellaneous files contain a small number of documents grouped together alphabetically by Senator Bush that were not extensive enough to have their own file.
  - Adoptions, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, 1961; 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Law, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Appointments, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous A, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous A, 1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Banking, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Banks, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Bar Association, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13-15)
  - Barge Canal, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Billboards, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - 1965 Budget, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19-21)
  - 1965 Budget The New York State Taxpayer (Flat-file 1)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Calendar, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Capital Punishment, 1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Chamber of Congress, 1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Cities, Affairs of, 1962; 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Civil Defense, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Civil Service, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Civil Service, 1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Civil Service Employees, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Codes, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Codes, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Commerce, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Committees, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Conservation, 1961-1963; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation, 1961-1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Conservation, 1963-1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Conservation, Belleayre, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Conservation, Belleayre, 1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Conservation, Lake Superior, 1961-1963; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Conservation (Land Parcels for Purchase), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Conservation (Picnic Areas), 1962; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Conservation, RIPS Retreat, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Consolidated Edison, 1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Correction, 1962-1963; 1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Correction Officers, 1964; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Court Reorganization, 1961; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Court Reorganization, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Delaware County, 1960; 1962-1963; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20-22)
  - Delaware County, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Delaware County, 1961; 1964-1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - Delaware County, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26-28)
  - Delaware County Schools, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Delaware County Veterans Service, 1961; 1963; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Delhi Ag and Tech, 1964; Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Delhi Ag and Tech School, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Dental Society, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous D, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous D, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Education, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5-9)
  - Education, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10-12)
  - Education, 1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13-15)
  - Educational Board Bill, 1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Election Law, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous E, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous E, 1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Family Court Act, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Farm Bureau, 1963; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Farm Bureau, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Federal, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Finance, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Finance Committee, 1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Firearms, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Firearms, 1965; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Fire Laws Committee, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Flags, 1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Full Crew, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 3 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31-32)
  - Miscellaneous F, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous F, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
  - Gambling, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Grange - New York State, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Greene County, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Greene County, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Greene County, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Greene County, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous G, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous G, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Health, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Health (Mental), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Hearings, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Highways, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Highways - General, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Highways - In District, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Highways - In District, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Highways - In District, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Horse Racing, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Housing, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Housing, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Human Rights, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Humane Slaughter, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous H, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous H, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Identification & Intelligence Project, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Insurance, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Insurance, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Insurance, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Internal Affairs, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Invitations, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33-34)
  - Miscellaneous I, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Jet Port, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Judicial Conference, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37-38)
  - Judiciary, 1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Junkyards, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous J, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous J, 1965; Undated (Box 4 (1-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous K, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous K, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Labor, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Labor, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5-7)
  - Legislation (Pending), 1959; 1960; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Legislation (Pending), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Legislative Bulletin, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Legislative Hopper, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Legislative Research, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Legislative Research Bulletins, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Legislature, 1963; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Legislature, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Liberty Amendment, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous L, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous L, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Mailing Lists, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Medical, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Meetings, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Mental Hygiene, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Minimum Wage, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23-24)
  - Moreland Commission, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25-27)
  - Motor Vehicles (General), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Motor Vehicles - Licenses, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Motor Vehicles (Requests), 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous M, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous M, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - New York, Affairs of the City of, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - New York City, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - New York Good Roads Association, 1963; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - New York State Automobile Association, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - New York State Conference of Mayors, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - New York State Conference of Mayors, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - New York State Council of Churches, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - New York State Council of Retail Merchants, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - New York State Grange, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - New York State Republican Committee, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - New York State's World's Fair, Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Newcombe, Lloyd, Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous N, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Off-Track Betting, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Off-Track Betting, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous O, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Penal Institutions, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Penal Law, 1962; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Penal Law, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Permanent Personal Registration, 1963; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Permanent Personal Registration, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Permanent Personal Registration, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Personal, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Politics, Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Politics, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Power Authority, 1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Professional Associations, Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Publicity, 1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Public Health, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Public Health & Welfare, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Public Relief & Welfare, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Public Service Commission, 1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Public Welfare, 1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Public Welfare, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Public Works, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Public Works, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Publisher Materials: Booklets, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Publisher Materials: Bulletins, 1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Publisher Materials: Legislative Daily Journal, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21-23)
  - Publisher Materials: Pamphlets, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Publisher Materials: Reports, 1963-1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25-29)
  - Miscellaneous P, 1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous P - [RESTRICTED], 1964; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Miscellaneous P, 1963; 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Quarter Horse Racing, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Q, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Racing, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Railroads, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Reapportionment, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Red Books & Manuals, 1963-1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Regents Scholarships, 1963; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Regents Scholarships, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40-41)
  - Releases by Senator, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Rent Control, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Rent Control, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Republican Committee, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Republican Committee, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Republican Newsletters, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Resolution, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Resolution 15, 1958; 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7-9)
  - Resolution 17, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Resolution 54, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Resolution 93, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Resolution 110, 1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Resolution 114, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Resolution 116, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Resolution 195, 1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Route 17, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Route 17, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Rules, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous R, 1962; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous R, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous R, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - St. George (Katharine), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - St. George (Katharine), 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Scholarships, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Schools, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26-27)
  - Schools (In Area), 1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - School Taxes, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Senate Employees, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Session Employees, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Sewage Disposal Program, 1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Snow Renewal, 1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Social Security, Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Special Session December, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - State Aid, 1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - State Aid - Per Capita, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - State Aid - Schools, 1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - State Aid - Schools, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - State Police, 1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - State Government News, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - State University, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 42-43)
  - State University of New York, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Sullivan County, 1884; 1964-1965; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Sullivan County, 1958; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Sullivan County, 1960-1962; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 47-48)
  - Sullivan County, 1961-1964; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous S, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous S, 1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous S, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Taxation, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Taxation, 1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Taxation - Cigarette Taxes, 1965; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Taxation - Gasoline Tax Use, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Taxation - Motor Vehicles, 1965; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Taxation - Sales Tax, 1965; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Teachers, 1963; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Teachers, 1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Teachers, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Teachers (Pension), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Teachers (Retirement), 1963; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Teachers (Retirement), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Teachers (Retirement), 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Temporary Commission on State Capital, 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Tuition, 1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous T, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous T, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Ulster County, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Ulster County, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Ulster County, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Ulster County (Wittenberg Park), 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Veterans Administration, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)